Ronald G. Becker Collection of Charles Eisenmann Photographs
Ronald G. Becker collection of Charles Eisenmann photographs
- Ronald G. Becker collection of miscellaneous circus freak photographs
  - 806 - Unidentified moss haired girl, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 807 - Zaluma Agara Circassian girl, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 808 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 809 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 810 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 811 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 812 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 813 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 814 - Zula Zulick Circassian queen, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 815 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 816 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 817 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 818 - Zoe Meleke Circassian, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 819 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 820 - Zoe Meleke Circassian, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 821 - Unidentified moss haired lady, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 822 - Zula Zingara Circassian lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 823 - Dearden Sisters dancers, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 824 - Leona Dari acrobat, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 825 - Albino family, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 826 - Albino family, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 827 - Albino family, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 828 - Albino girl, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 829 - Albino girl, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 830 - Little Ida albino, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 831 - Albino twin children, 1865 (Box 9)
  - 832 - Albino lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 833 - Aggie Zolidra albino, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 834 - Unidentified albino man, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 835 - Albino man, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 836 - Zula Luti albino, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 837 - Albino lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 838 - Aggie Zolutia albino, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 839 - Albino lady, 1870 (Box 9)
  - 840 - Mille Lucille albino, 1875 (Box 9)
  - 841 - Millie Lamar mind reader, 1897 (Box 10)
  - 842 - P.T. Barnum, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 843 - Jo Jo, the dog faced boy, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 843a - Jo Jo, the dog faced boy, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 844 - Mahphoon the Burmese hairy woman, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 845 - Unidentified rubber skin man, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 846 - J.C. Bradeen skeleton man, 1880 (Box 10)
  - 847 - Piebald baby, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 848 - Piebald black boy, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 849 - Alligator skin man, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 850 - ? Edwards tattooed man, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 851 - Frank Howard tattooed man, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 852 - Unidentified tattooed lady, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 853 - Ann Howard tattooed lady, 1880 (Box 10)
  - 854 - Annie Howard tattooed lady, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 855 - Irene Woodward tattooed lady, 1880 (Box 10)
  - 856 - Eli Bowen legless wonder, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 857 - Eli Bowen, wife and family, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 858 - Charles Tripp armless wonder, 1880 (Box 10)
  - 859 - W.L. Stuart armless and legless man, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 860 - Unidentified legless lady, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 861 - Unidentified girl without legs, 1895 (Box 10)
  - 862 - Unidentified girl without legs, 1895 (Box 10)
  - 863 - Laloo boy with parasitic twin, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 864 - Francisco Lentini boy with three legs, 1899 (Box 10)
  - 865 - Francisco Lentini boy with three legs, 1901 (Box 10)
  - 866 - Mille Christine black Siamese twins, 1895 (Box 10)
  - 867 - Tocci Bros. Siamese twins, 1890 (Box 10)
  - 868 - Tocci Bros. Siamese twins, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 869 - Tocci Bros. Siamese twins, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 870 - Lady without shoulder blades, 1880 (Box 10)
  - 871 - Zip and Ash pinhead boxers, 1890 (Box 10)
  - 872 - Pinheads, 1900 (Box 10)
  - 873 - Erwin Smith man with eight foot beard, 1880 (Box 10)
  - 874 - Sig Arcaris knife thrower, 1895 (Box 10)
  - 875 - Signor Poddreth? strong man, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 876 - Lady with five alligators, 1895 (Box 10)
  - 877 - Unidentified male costumed performers, 1895 (Box 10)
  - 878 - Unidentified wild west show family, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 879 - Sioux Indians, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 880 - Horse with long mane, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 881 - Gen. Tom Thumb and wife, 1881 (Box 10)
  - 882 - Count Magri, Baron Rosebud, and Lavinia Warren midgets, 1890 (Box 10)
  - 883 - The Magri's midgets, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 884 - The Italian midgets, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 885 - Count and Countess Magri midgets, 1880 (Box 10)
  - 885a - Mrs. Tom Thumb midget, 1895 (Box 10)
  - 886 - Little Lord Robert midget, 1890 (Box 10)
  - 887 - Unidentified midget couple, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 888 - Princess Ida and Gen. Totman midgets, 1888 (Box 10)
  - 889 - Unidentified midget lady, 1890 (Box 10)
  - 890 - Unidentified midget lady, 1890 (Box 10)
  - 891 - Unidentified elderly midget lady, 1895 (Box 10)
  - 892 - Unidentified midget lady, 1890 (Box 10)
  - 893 - Unidentified midget couple, 1895 (Box 10)
  - 894 - Liliput Trio midgets, 1895 (Box 10)
  - 895 - Unidentified midget, 1890 (Box 10)
  - 896 - Unidentified midget, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 897 - Che Mah Chinese Dwarf, 1885 (Box 10)
  - 898 - The Liliputians midget troupe, 1890 (Box 10)
  - 899 - Midget troupe, 1890 (Box 10)
  - 900 - Col. Speck midget, 1880 (Box 10)
  - 901 - Col. Speck midget, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 902 - Col. Speck midget, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 903 - Unidentified midget boy, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 904 - Gen. Rihnback midget, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 905 - Maj. Mite midget, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 906 - Unidentified dwarf sisters, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 907 - Henrietta Moritz midget, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 908 - Fannie Bristal midget, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 909 - (Box 11)
  - 910 - Unidentified midget lady, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 911 - Unidentified midget lady, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 912 - Commodore Cornelius midget, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 913 - Unidentified midget lady, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 914 - Unidentified midget lady, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 915 - Maj. Tot midget, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 916 - The Little Esquimaux Lady midget, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 917 - The Fillipino midgets, 1890 (Box 11)
  - 918 - Unidentified man with snakes, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 919 - Unidentified lady with snakes, 1890 (Box 11)
  - 920 - Zulu Aeyers snake charmer, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 921 - Young girl with snakes, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 922 - Nelli Leona snake charmer (Box 11)
  - 923 - Millie Betra serpent queen, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 924 - Unidentified lady with snake, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 925 - Unidentified lady with snakes, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 926 - Col. Orr giant, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 927 - Mr. and Mrs. O'Brien giants, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 928 - Ben Brown giant, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 929 - Unidentified giant, 1895 (Box 11)
  - 930 - Col. Ruth Goshon giant, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 931 - Col. Ruth Goshon giant, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 932 - Col. Ruth Goshon giant, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 933 - Chang Yu Sing Chinese giant, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 934 - George Robinson giant, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 935 - Ella Ewing giant, 1890 (Box 11)
  - 936 - Rosa Wedsted giant, 1895 (Box 11)
  - 937 - Col. Wm. Baker boy giant, 1890 (Box 11)
  - 938 - Thomas Brockman black giant, 1895 (Box 11)
  - 939 - Unidentified black giant lady, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 940 - Capt. Smith Cook giant, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 941 - Annie Jones bearded lady, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 942 - Annie Jones bearded lady, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 943 - Madame Myers (Delait) bearded lady, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 944 - Madame Myers bearded lady, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 945 - Madame Myers bearded lady, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 946 - Ida Williams fat lady, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 947 - Baby Emma fat girl, 1905 (Box 11)
  - 948 - Ada Briggs - fat lady, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 949 - Ada Briggs - fat lady, 1883 (Box 11)
  - 950 - Anna Bell fat lady, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 951 - Unidentified fat lady, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 952 - Dela Howard fat lady, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 953 - Maggie Clark fat lady, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 954 - Unidentified black fat lady, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 955 - Madame June fat lady with snake, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 956 - Col. C.H. Jackson fat man, 1905 (Box 11)
  - 957 - David Navarro fat boy, 1880 (Box 11)
  - 958 - Frank Williams fat boy, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 959 - John Craig fat man, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 960 - Unidentified albino girl, 1885 (Box 11)
  - 961 - Unidentified albino girl, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 962 - Millie Lammar albino girl, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 963 - Millie Lammar albino girl (Box 12)
  - 964 - Millie Lammar albino girl, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 965 - Unidentified albino girl, 1890 (Box 12)
  - 966 - Unidentified albino girl, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 967 - Wm. and Lizzie Cavaliers albino twins, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 968 - Unzie albino man, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 969 - Charles and Danny Hadley albino twins, 1870 (Box 12)
  - 970 - Unidentified albino girl, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 971 - Unidentified albino girl, 1900 (Box 12)
  - 972 - Unidentified albino lady, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 973 - Mary Sutherland long haired lady, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 974 - Dora Sutherland long haired lady, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 975 - Naomi Sutherland long haired lady, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 976 - Grace Sutherland long haired lady, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 977 - Unidentified Sutherland sister long haired lady, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 978 - Unidentified Sutherland sister long haired lady, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 979 - Jessie Allyne long haired lady, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 980 - Nellie Owen long haired lady, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 981 - Madame Milo long haired lady, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 982 - Etta Lake elastic skin lady, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 983 - Unidentified lady with short hair, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 984 - Unidentified tattooed lady, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 985 - Unidentified moss haired girl, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 986 - Unidentified moss haired girl, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 987 - Unidentified Circassian lady, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 988 - Miss Uno snake charmer (?), 1890 (Box 12)
  - 989 - Miss Uno moss hair, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 990 - Miss Uno moss hair, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 991 - Miss Uno moss hair, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 992 - Unidentified moss haired girl, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 993 - Unidentified moss haired girl, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 994 - Zola moss haired girl, 1890 (Box 12)
  - 995 - Mille Irene (?) acrobat, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 996 - Baby Venus young girl with large breasts, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 997 - Miss Inez Electric Queen (?), 1885 (Box 12)
  - 998 - Werner and Bell ??, 1890 (Box 12)
  - 999 - Victoria Sutherland long haired lady, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 1000 - ??? fat boy, 1885 (Box 12)
  - 1001 - Filipino midgets, 1905 (Box 12)
  - 1002 - Thomas Longley fat man, 1890 (Box 12)
  - 1003 - Outdoor scene of Barnum, Bailey, & Hutchinson Circus Train Wreck, 1889 (Box 12)
  - 1004 - Outdoor scene of Barnum, Bailey, & Hutchinson Circus Train Wreck, 1889 (Box 12)
  - 1005 - Long haired lady, 1875 (Box 12)
  - 1006 - Fat lady, 1896 (Box 12)
  - 1007 - Barnum's American Museum after the fire, 1870 (Box 12)
  - 1008 - Ruins of Barnum's Museum, NY, 1868 (Box 12)
  - 1009 - Virginia Dare famous trapeze artist, 1870 (Box 12)
  - 1010 - Zuluma Agara Circassian girl, 1870 (Box 12)
  - 1011 - Unidentified clown, 1875 (Box 12)
  - 1012 - P.T. Barnum and party at Yosemite Falls, 1870 (Box 12)
  - 1012a - Robert Ruy (?) and wife (Box 12)
- Ronald G. Becker collection of sideshow memorabilia (Box 12)
  - 1013 - The Midget's Palace, 1930 (Box 12)
  - 1014 - Bingham Ventriloquist, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 1015 - Zoe Meleke, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 1016 - Marvelous Midget, 1880 (Box 12)
  - 1017 - Original autograph P.T. Barnum, 1882 (Box 12)
  - 1018 - (Box 12)
  - 1019 - Siamese twins Barnum's Great Moral Show, 1870 (Box 12)
  - 1020 - Mille Christine, renowned two headed lady, 1883 (Box 12)
  - 1021 - Choung Chi Lang giant, 1880 (Box 13)
  - 1022 - The Giants M.V. Bates and wife, 1879 (Box 13)
  - 1023 - The Giants M.V. Bates and wife, 1879; duplicate of #1022 (Box 13)
  - 1024 - Capt. Costentenus tattooed man, 1877 (Box 13)
  - 1025 - G.B. Bunnell's Museum, 1875 (Box 16)
  - 1026 - What we know about Wano and Plutano Wild Men of Borneo booklet, 1893?; duplicate of #1027 with different color cover (Box 16)
  - 1027 - What we know about Wano and Plutano Wild Men of Borneo booklet, 1893?; duplicate of #1026 with different color cover (Box 16)
  - 1028 - The History and travels of Barnum's $100,000 Rice Family booklet, 1870 (Box 16)
  - 1029 - Sketch of Gen. Tom Thumb and wife, 1868 (Box 16)
  - 1030 - Gen. Tom Thumb's three year tour around the world booklet, 1872 (Box 16)
  - 1031 - History of Major N.G.W. Winner and wife midgets booklet, 1890 (Box 16)
  - 1032 - Life of Isaac W. Sprague the Living Skeleton booklet, 1882 (Box 16)
  - 1033 - (Box 16)
  - 1034 - History of Miss Annie Jones, Barnum's Esau Lady booklet, 1885 (Box 16)
  - 1035 - Illustrated catalogue and guide book to Barnum's American Museum, 1860 (Box 16)
  - 1036 - Sketch of the life of Gen. Tom Thumb booklet, 1847 (Box 16)
  - 1037 - Life of the Siamese twins booklet, 1853 (Box 16)
  - 1038 - Life and sufferings of Leonard Trask wonderful invalid booklet, 1857 (Box 16)
  - 1039 - History and life of Unzie, the Australian aboriginal beauty booklet, 1893 (Box 16)
  - 1040 - Laloo booklet, 1888 (Box 16)
  - 1041 - Domestic habits of the Siamese twins booklet, 1850 (Box 16)
  - 1042 - Sketch of the life of Charles Decker smallest man in the world, 1867 (Box 16)
  - 1043 - History of animals and leading curiosities contained in P.T. Barnum's Greatest Show on Earth booklet, 1877 (Box 16)
  - 1044 - The Strand Magazine "Pictures on the human skin", Feb. 1897 (Box 16)
  - 1045 - The Strand Magazine A"Sideshows", Apr. 1897 (Box 16)
  - 1046 - The Realm, a magazine of marvels "Some curious physical freaks", 1903 (Box 16)
  - 1047-1111 - Early postcards, 1895-1940; 64 items (Box 13)
  - 1112 - Life and adventures of Capt. Costentenus the tattooed Greek Prince, written by himself booklet, 1881 (Box 17)
  - 1112a - Life history of Francesco Lentini three legged wonder booklet, 1900 (Box 17)
  - 1112b - Francesco Lentini three legged man card, 1920 (Box 17)
  - 1113 - Chiquita lady midget photo pin, 1896 (Box 17)
  - 1114 - Unidentified midget lady photo pin, 1890 (Box 17)
  - 1115 - Robinson show photo pin, 1895 (Box 17)
  - 1116 - U.S. Commemorative Silver Half Dollar, obverse with P.T. Barnum, 1836; 1936 (Box 17)
  - 1117 - Barnum's American Museum, message written and autographed by P.T. Barnum on his stationery, 1860 (Box 17)
  - 1118 - P.T. Barnum's Great London Circus and Chang, the Chinese Giant medallion, 1881 (Box 17)
  - 1119 - P.T. Barnum's Greatest Show on Earth broadside oversized, 1877 (Map-case 1, Drawer 1)
  - 1120 - Siamese twins, united brothers, 1865 (Box 18)
  - 1121 - The wonderful albino family, 1865 (Box 18)
  - 1122 - Gen. Tom Thumb and wife, Comm. Nutt, and Minnie Warren, by Currier and Ives, 1863 (Box 19)
  - 1122a - Listed under #1187 on supplementary list Gen. Tom Thumb, by Currier and Ives, 1863 (Box 19)
  - 1123-01 - Jones twins joined at buttocks (Box 14)
  - 1123-2 - Pasqual Pinon two headed Mexican (Box 14)
  - 1123-3 - Mr. & Mrs. Long tallest married couple (Box 14)
  - 1123-4 - Robert Wadlow tallest man on record (Box 14)
  - 1123-5 - Flip the Frog Boy tiny legs, normal body (Box 14)
  - 1123-6 - Vin Linnie 1940 no hands, tiny foot growing from shoulder blade (Box 14)
  - 1123-7 - Myrtle Corbin 4 legged woman (Box 14)
  - 1123-8 - Myrtle Corbin 4 legged woman (Box 14)
  - 1123-9 - Frances O'Conner no arms (Box 14)
  - 1123-10 - Frances O'Conner no arms (Box 14)
  - 1123-11 - Charles B. Tripple, no arms, pedaling; Eli Brown, no legs, steering (Box 14)
  - 1123-12 - Francisco Lettini three legged man (Box 14)
  - 1123-13 - Francisco Lettini three legged man (Box 14)
  - 1123-14 - Avilla J. Camerlin six toes on each foot (Box 14)
  - 1123-15 - Avilla J. Camerlin and granddaughter each had six toes (Box 14)
  - 1123-16 - John Eck half man, no legs (Box 14)
  - 1123-17 - John Eck half man, no legs (Box 14)
  - 1123-18 - Busten Scott largest feet in the world (Box 14)
  - 1123-19 - Joan Whisnant no arms (Box 14)
  - 1123-20 - Myrtle Corbin 4 legged woman (Box 14)
  - 1123-21 - Charley Barnett the seal man, flipper like arms (Box 14)
  - 1123-22 - Eli Bowen and one of his many children legless man (Box 14)
  - 1123-23 - Violetta armless, legless woman (Box 14)
  - 1123-24 - Sadie Slitz seal woman, flipper like arms (Box 14)
  - 1123-25 - Prof. C.H. Townsend one legged man (Box 14)
  - 1123-26 - Joe very large fingers (Box 14)
  - 1123-27 - Lavonda legless woman and husband Alva Evans clown (Box 14)
  - 1123-28 - Freida Pushnik armless and legless woman (Box 14)
  - 1123-29 - Baby with one head and two bodies, 1940 (Box 14)
  - 1123-30 - Another view of baby with one head and two bodies (Box 14)
  - 1123-31 - Laloo Indian boy parasite twin (Box 14)
  - 1123-32 - Baby with two heads, one body, 1938 (Box 14)
  - 1123-33 - Betty Williams parasite twin (Box 14)
  - 1123-34 - Baby with tail, no eyes, no nostril, large ears (Box 14)
  - 1123-35 - Korean twins joined at breast bone, 1903 (Box 14)
  - 1123-36 - Siamese twins one head, two bodies (Box 14)
  - 1123-37 - Margarite Clark parasite twin (Box 14)
  - 1123-38 - Betty Williams parasite twin (Box 14)
  - 1123-39 - Siamese twins joined at head (Box 14)
  - 1123-40 - Permal Sami of India parasite twin (Box 14)
  - 1123-41 - Big Liz fat lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-42 - The Farmer Fat family 1941 parents, Annie, Gloria, John, Paul, James (Box 14)
  - 1123-43 - Baby Ruth Pontico fat lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-44 - Bonita the midget fat girl (Box 14)
  - 1123-45 - Baby Betty fat lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-46 - Mamie fat lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-47 - Baby Irene fat lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-48 - Baby Irene fat lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-49 - Dainty Dotty fat lady, 1941 (Box 14)
  - 1123-50 - Major Mite age 22, midget (Box 14)
  - 1123-51 - Ytura pygmies, toured country in 1940 (Box 14)
  - 1123-52 - Major Littlefingers and wife midgets (Box 14)
  - 1123-53 - Doll family midgets, with Dainty Dotty fat lady, 1948 (Box 14)
  - 1123-54 - Princess Wee Wee midget (Box 14)
  - 1123-55 - George Auger giant with Tom Sordie midget (Box 14)
  - 1123-56 - Londy world's tallest lady, 1907 (Box 14)
  - 1123-57 - Mildred giant lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-58 - John Petursson Iceland giant (Box 14)
  - 1123-59 - Robert Wadlow giant (Box 14)
  - 1123-60 - Chang Yu San Chinese giant (Box 14)
  - 1123-61 - Londy giant lady, 1907 (Box 14)
  - 1123-62 - Fischers tallest couple with an elephant (Box 14)
  - 1123-63 - Aloa alligator boy, reptile like skin (Box 14)
  - 1123-64 - Knotty Man covered with lumps (Box 14)
  - 1123-65 - Arthur Loos rubber skinned man (Box 14)
  - 1123-66 - Susie elephant skinned girl (Box 14)
  - 1123-67 - Agnes C. Schmidt rubber skinned from hips to knees (Box 14)
  - 1123-68 - Alzora Green short, stubby arms and legs (Box 14)
  - 1123-69 - The Williams family black & white spotted skin (Box 14)
  - 1123-70 - Ossified Harry stone man, he was rigid and hard (Box 14)
  - 1123-71 - Allistaire MacWilkie 12 foot long whiskers (Box 14)
  - 1123-72 - Unidentified man from a tribe in Philippines that grew tails (Box 14)
  - 1123-73 - Seven Sutherland sisters (Box 14)
  - 1123-74 - Lionel, the lion faced boy (Box 14)
  - 1123-75 - Hanka Kelter longest hair (Box 14)
  - 1123-76 - Eleander Tarantino 1944 a tuft of hair grows from back (Box 14)
  - 1123-77 - Jo Jo, the dog faced boy (Box 14)
  - 1123-78 - Priscilla hairy bodied lady, with whiskers (Box 14)
  - 1123-79 - Eko and Iko sheep headed men, hair like wool (Box 14)
  - 1123-80 - Mangebetu woman from Congo sculptured hair (Box 14)
  - 1123-81 - Dora Sutherland 1900, hair drags on floor (Box 14)
  - 1123-82 - Francis Murkhey bearded lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-83 - Ram Sam covered with wool like a sheep (Box 14)
  - 1123-84 - Dorenna circus queen with bushy hair (Box 14)
  - 1123-85 - Krao the missing link girl, covered with hair (Box 14)
  - 1123-86 - Krao the missing link girl (Box 14)
  - 1123-87 - William Barrow skinny man (Box 14)
  - 1123-88 - Harry Jones skeleton man (Box 14)
  - 1123-89 - Slim Jim Milton Malone skeleton man (Box 14)
  - 1123-90 - Albert Alberta brother/sister, each half male, half female (Box 14)
  - 1123-91 - Joe Ann LaFrance half female, half male (Box 14)
  - 1123-92 - Bobby Kork half female, half male (Box 14)
  - 1123-93 - Mary Ann Bevens ugliest woman (Box 14)
  - 1123-94 - Big lipped Ubangi woman from central Africa (Box 14)
  - 1123-95 - Pop eyed Perry ability to pop eyes out on his cheeks (Box 14)
  - 1123-96 - Leonard Hanstein could hold 4 billiard balls in his mouth, 1938 (Box 14)
  - 1123-97 - Big lipped Ubangi woman (Box 14)
  - 1123-98 - Ubangi women big lipped women (Box 14)
  - 1123-99 - The Bird Woman of Ringling Bros. (Box 14)
  - 1123-100 - Burmese woman (Box 14)
  - 1123-101 - Ubangi woman large lipped woman (Box 14)
  - 1123-102 - Popeye looks like Popeye the sailor man (Box 14)
  - 1123-103 - Koo Koo birdwoman dancing with Lip and Schlitzi the pinheads (Box 14)
  - 1123-104 - Godino and Apexia pinhead brother and sister from Burma (Box 14)
  - 1123-105 - Lip the Barnum "What is it" (Box 14)
  - 1123-106 - Christina the elephant skinned girl (Box 14)
  - 1123-107 - Mignon the penguin girl, 1950 (Box 14)
  - 1123-108 - Leo Kongee "human blockhead" poked pins in face (Box 14)
  - 1123-109 - Martin Burkjardt can suck in his stomach until it meets backbone (Box 14)
  - 1123-110 - Leone Young 1938 professional fire eater (Box 14)
  - 1123-111 - Corpse that was never buried (Box 14)
  - 1123-112 - Unzi most famous of Albino people, had very bushy hair (Box 14)
  - 1123-113 - Lucasie family bushy haired albinos (Box 14)
  - 1123-114 - Clicko with group of midgets and Artoria tattooed lady, 1925 (Box 14)
  - 1123-115 - Clicko a bushman captured from head hunters, 1930 (Box 14)
  - 1123-116 - Charlotte Hoyer a professional sword swallower (Box 14)
  - 1123-117 - Myrtle tattooed lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-118 - Mary and Margaret Gibb American Siamese twins (Box 14)
  - 1123-119 - Tattooed lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-120 - Ruth Ullrich of Germany tattooed lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-121 - Jenny Quigley the midget known as the "Scottish Queen" (Box 14)
  - 1123-122 - A German lady with birds and butterflies tattooed on her breasts (Box 14)
  - 1123-123 - A Japanese lady tattooed back (Box 14)
  - 1123-124 - Japanese man and woman, both tattooed (Box 14)
  - 1123-125 - Major Mite with Ringling Bros. (Box 14)
  - 1123-126 - Mrs. Billy White tattooed lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-127 - Princess Marguerite midget (Box 14)
  - 1123-128 - A tattooed lady moons and palm trees (Box 14)
  - 1123-129 - Unidentified tattooed lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-130 - Unidentified tattooed lady having more tattoos added (Box 14)
  - 1123-131 - Unidentified tattooed lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-132 - Unidentified man carries bowels outside his body (Box 14)
  - 1123-133 - Unidentified man carries bowels outside his body (Box 14)
  - 1123-134 - Princess Pontus Amazon giantess (Box 14)
  - 1123-135 - Filipino boy whose left hand is 10x larger than normal (Box 14)
  - 1123-136 - Minnie Ha Ha the small pinhead woman, 1916 (Box 14)
  - 1123-137 - Baby one head, two bodies (Box 14)
  - 1123-138 - Jack Earle giant with normal man (Box 14)
  - 1123-139 - Mary and Arrita Siamese twins born in Mexico City in, 1910 (Box 14)
  - 1123-140 - Smiling Alice fat lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-141 - Jolly Mary fat lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-142 - Alpine fat lady (Box 14)
  - 1123-143 - Jolly Babe the Farmer fat girl (Box 15)
  - 1123-144 - Unidentified fat lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-145 - Jolly Ethel" fat lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-146 - Jolly Trixie" fat lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-147 - Unidentified fat man (Box 15)
  - 1123-148 - Unidentified fat lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-149 - Jolly Nelli fat lady with John Robinson Circus (Box 15)
  - 1123-150 - Alice Wade fat lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-151 - Eli Brown legless man, feet growing out of hips (Box 15)
  - 1123-152 - Hazel Morris and daughter Jackie dwarfs (Box 15)
  - 1123-153 - Grady Stiles Lobster Boy deformed hands (Box 15)
  - 1123-154 - Grace McDaniels "mule faced" woman deformed face (Box 15)
  - 1123-155 - Mule faced woman (Box 15)
  - 1123-156 - Bambolla human monkey man is skin and bones (Box 15)
  - 1123-157 - Susi the elephant skin girl (Box 15)
  - 1123-158 - Baby Doll Waites fat lady (Box 15)